A Guide to the Edward L. Stone/Borderland Coal Company Papers
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Edward L. Stone Personal Papers
  - American Anti-Boycott Assoc. - mentions backlash of business against unions, 1909, 1911 -1912; (2 folders) (Box Box 370)
  - Circular letters sent out by S. P. & M. Co., 1907 -1908 (Box Box 370)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Engines", 1909 (Box Box 370)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence - including The Panama Canal, 1910 (Box Box 370)
  - Miscellaneous "C", 1909 -1911 (Box Box 370)
  - Correspondence "G" - topics: G. G. Gooch Jr., 1916 -1920 (Box Box 371)
  - Correspondence "E-F" - topics: Horace M. Engle, Henry D. Estabrook, Foote & Davies, Charles R. Fishburn, The Evening Times, 1913 -1919 (Box Box 371)
  - Correspondence "F" - topics: Falk Photographer, Charles B. Fishburn, William A. Field Co., Robert and Lawrence Fell, First National Bank, Federal Reserve Bank of Richmond, J. B. Fishburn, William F. C. Fellers, 1910 -1920 (Box Box 371)
  - Miscellaneous letters, 1919, 1925, 1931; (3 folders) (Box Box 371)
  - Tax returns - to 1922, 1916 -1922 (Box Box 374)
  - Detail monthly statements, 1927 -1928; (2 folders) (Box Box 374)
  - Income tax returns - income tax returns for Mrs. Minnie F. Stone, 1920 -1927 (Box Box 374)
  - Monthly statements (personal) - Stone's personal finances, 1929 -1930; (2 folders) (Box Box 374)
  - American Contractors Co., 1905 -1910 (Box Box 375)
  - Correspondence - topics: M. M. Caldwell, E. H. Kebler, Anti-toxic Cigarette Machine Co., American Industries, American Embassy Assoc., Acme Math Co., American Academy of Political Social Science, advertisements, 1908 -1911 (Box Box 375)
  - Hollins College - co-educational proposed co-ordinate college at Charlottesville, 1929 (Box Box 375)
  - Stocks and bonds, 1910-1911, 1920; (4 folders) (Box Box 377)
  - Correspondence - topics: Stone Printing & Mfg. Co., miscellaneous, scouting, stage, 1920 (Box Box 377)
  - Correspondence "S" - topics: Steamship Tour Circulars, S. W. Stone, E. B. Stone, State College for Women, O. W. Stone, 1909 -1911 (Box Box 377)
  - Miscellaneous "He-Hn", 1931 -1935 (Box Box 377)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence - topics: Ogontz School, National Freight Traffic Golf Assoc., National Assoc. of Advertising Novelty Mfg., M. Oshima, 1900 -1915; (2 folders) (Box Box 379)
  - National Exchange Bank, 1909 -1915 (Box Box 379)
  - Correspondence "H", 1935 -1938 (Box Box 379)
  - Miscellaneous "Fa-Fn", 1930 -1935; (2 folders) (Box Box 380)
  - Miscellaneous "M", 1920 -1926 (Box Box 380)
  - Miscellaneous "R", 1920 -1926 (Box Box 380)
  - Miscellaneous "N", 1921 -1924 (Box Box 380)
  - Bureau of War Risk Insurance, 1918 -1922 (Box Box 381)
  - Miscellaneous "C", 1920 -1925 (Box Box 381)
  - Miscellaneous "D", 1920 -1926 (Box Box 381)
  - Miscellaneous "P", 1920 -1925 (Box Box 381)
  - Correspondence "M", 1935 -1936 (Box Box 381)
  - Miscellaneous "Ka-Kk", 1932 -1936 (Box Box 381)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence - topics: J. A. Hatcher, M. R. Jackson, reports and statements, I. O. Johnson, miscellaneous "Ne-Ni", 1931 -1935; (2 folders) (Box Box 382)
  - Melbert B. Cary Jr. - president of the Woolly Whale, 1931 -1935 (Box Box 382)
  - Edward L. Stone - to and from secretary, 1930 -1934 (Box Box 382)
  - Mr. George Carter, Public Printer, Washington, D.C., 1932 -1934 (Box Box 382)
  - Jeffersonian Democrats, 1936 (Box Box 383)
  - Miscellaneous "J", 1933 -1935 (Box Box 383)
  - Miscellaneous "I-J", 1936 -1937 (Box Box 383)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "C", 1934 -1935 (Box Box 383)
  - Miscellaneous "Me-Mn", 1934 -1935 (Box Box 384)
  - Mrs. Jean Clough, 1932 -1938; (2 folders) (Box Box 384)
  - Miscellaneous "L", 1921 -1926 (Box Box 385)
  - Miscellaneous "J", 1921 -1924 (Box Box 385)
  - Miscellaneous "K", 1922 -1924 (Box Box 385)
  - Miscellaneous "H", 1920 -1925 (Box Box 385)
  - Miscellaneous "F", 1920 -1926 (Box Box 385)
  - Miscellaneous "G", 1920 -1926 (Box Box 385)
  - Southwest Virginia Trust Co., 1915 -1917 (Box Box 386)
  - Mrs. M. F. Stone, 1917 (Box Box 386)
  - Miscellaneous "D-E", 1917 (Box Box 386)
  - Jordan-Stabler Co., 1916 -1918 (Box Box 386)
  - Miscellaneous "H-I", 1915 -1918 (Box Box 386)
  - Miscellaneous "J", 1916 -1917 (Box Box 386)
  - Miscellaneous "T-Z", 1915 -1917 (Box Box 386)
  - Magazines, 1915 (Box Box 387)
  - Correspondence "M" - topics: A. W. McClure, Munich School, miscellaneous English letters, Mediterranean cruise, C. E. Michael, 1909 -1915 (Box Box 387)
  - Correspondence "L" - topics: L. E. Lookabill, W. C. Locker, W. H. Lewis, 1911 -1915 (Box Box 387)
  - Miscellaneous "L-M", 1912 -1915 (Box Box 387)
  - Miscellaneous "J", 1907 -1914 (Box Box 387)
  - Miscellaneous bills and letters, 1903 -1916; (2 folders) (Box Box 388)
  - Correspondence - topics: William Yule, Barry Zaring, West Virginia Inspection Bureau, Whitehead & Hoag Co., Norman Walker, 1909 -1916 (Box Box 388)
  - Miscellaneous "W", 1908 -1915 (Box Box 388)
  - Shenandoah Club and Savannah Chamber of Commerce, 1911, 1917 (Box Box 388)
  - Standard Cost Finding Service Go., 1913 (Box Box 388)
  - Correspondence "E" - topics: Exchange Lumber Co., Employees Empire Casualty Co., Electric Storage Battery Co., Electric Renovator Mfg. Co, 1908 -1912 (Box Box 389)
  - Miscellaneous "F", 1910 -1912 (Box Box 389)
  - Harris Forbes & Co. and John J. Lincoln, 1915 -1916 (Box Box 389)
  - Miscellaneous "A-G", 1913 -1918 (Box Box 389)
  - Miscellaneous "L-S", 1915 -1916 (Box Box 389)
  - Model Garage, 1915 -1918 (Box Box 389)
  - Roanoke Rotary Club - miscellaneous and general correspondence; topics: Community Chest Fund, Foreign Rotary Clubs, Rotary Conference, 1921 -1925; (4 folders) (Box Box 392)
  - Correspondence "Bap-Bau" - very abbreviated business (especially personal purchases) correspondences with: C. J. Baughman, Battle Creek Sanitarium, Charles Austin Bates, W. B. Bates, Baseball Assoc., Barnett Bros., W. F. Barnes, O. B. Barker, Barger, J. F. Barbour & Co., Baptist Times, 1904 -1908 (Box Box 393)
  - Correspondence "Bal-Ban" - topics: Balke Mfg. Co., Baldwin's Detectives, Daniel Baker, A. R. Bailey Mfg. Co., D. I. Bachman, Mr. and Mrs. James A. Bane, 1900 -1908 (Box Box 393)
  - Magazines - subscription offers, ca. 1916; (2 folders) (Box Box 393)
  - Correspondence "R" - very brief, personal business correspondence with: Roanoke Water Power Co., R. A. Hughes; Robertson, Hall, & Woods; Rhode & Brand Press, Daniel Robb, W. E. Robertson, H. S. Rominger, O. Howard Royer, Roycroft Shop (books), Ryland & Ranken (jewelers), 1900 -1908 (Box Box 394)
  - Correspondence "Ca-Ce" - personal letters to/from: J. E. Cattin, S. K. Campbell, W. C. Campbell, Carpenter & Boxley, Charles E. Caspari, Century Bank, 1899 -1907 (Box Box 394)
  - Correspondence "Ch-Cl" - personal private business letters to/from: A. M. Chandler, Chesapeake & Western Co., Cheniere Land & Lumber Co., E. C. Chittum, Clarence W. Clark, A. S. Clark, 1899 -1907 (Box Box 394)
  - Tiffany & Co. - about purchases of medals to honor Stone Printing Co. officers, 1909 -1913 (Box Box 395)
  - Miss M. F. Stone - personal correspondence between Mary Fred and Stone, 1909 -1915 (Box Box 395)
  - Miscellaneous "R" - personal business letters about or with: Roanoke Banking, Charles P. Rogers, Ramsey Wheeler Co., real estate, Regal Shoe Co., H. A. Redford, J. D. Rhodes, Riddleberger & Roper (brokers), John O. Richards (printers), F. H. Richardson (photographers), Richards Chair Panel Co., C. E Roagan, Roanoke Building Assoc., J. M. Rodger, 1902 -1908 (Box Box 395)
  - Autos - fliers from dealers to promote sales and showroom openings, 1930 -1931 (Box Box 396)
  - Bank notes "A-F" - issued to Stone, using stocks as collateral, 1929 -1934 (Box Box 396)
  - Bank notes "G-Q", 1929 -1934 (Box Box 396)
  - Bank notes "R-Z", 1929 -1934 (Box Box 396)
  - A.B.C. 12 Miscellaneous - circular letters from American Academy of Political Sciences, American Defense Society, etc., 1916 -1917 (Box Box 397)
  - 13 "D-E" Miscellaneous - mostly from American Exporter; all circular letters and ads for various clubs, organizations, sales outfits, 1916 -1918 (Box Box 397)
  - Atlantic Deeper Waterways Assoc. - Stone was a member of this outfit that supported the improvement of inland waterways - letters and announcements of meetings, 1911, 1912 (Box Box 397)
  - American Defense Society - group to encourage military preparedness, 1915 -1917 (Box Box 397)
  - Hotels and summer resorts - brochures and letters of welcome, 1909 -1911 (Box Box 397)
  - Miscellaneous "H" - letters to/from: Hotel Roanoke; Hatman, the Crofut & Knapp Co.; V. Helvestine, V. L. Henderson; A. E. Hamilton, Hancock-Harvey Co., Harvey Hill, Huggins & Bates, Elbert Hubbard, Joseph Hreu, J. S. Holmes, A. B. Hammond, etc.- letters are either personal, or they concern private business (purchases, reservations, etc.), 1903 -1915 (Box Box 397)
  - Roanoke Hospital - mostly fund raising letters; Stone was on the Board of Directors, 1900 -1909 (Box Box 398)
  - Roanoke College - request for contribution, 1900 -1909 (Box Box 398)
  - Roanoke Country Club - about dues, events, etc., 1900 -1909 (Box Box 398)
  - Roanoke Hydraulic Co. - about stock purchases, 1900 -1909 (Box Box 398)
  - Roanoke and Fincastle - about a proposed railroad between the two cities, 1900 -1909 (Box Box 398)
  - Roanoke, Va. - about local and political (tour) issues, 1900 -1909 (Box Box 398)
  - Roanoke Cycle Co. - correspondence with this hobby shop about photo supplies. including several negatives, 1900 -1909 (Box Box 398)
  - Trips - ads for touring services, 1915 (Box Box 398)
  - Twine Mills Corp. - letters to/from Stone as a director of this company, 1914 -1915 (Box Box 398)
  - Times Investment Corp. - about stock purchases, 1910 -1915 (Box Box 398)
  - J. B. Thomas - about a $600 personal loan, 1914 (Box Box 398)
  - Joseph A. Turner - about sale of a birds-eye view of Hollins, Va. to its city manager, 1911 -1914 (Box Box 398)
  - Unions - clippings, 1913 -1915 (Box Box 398)
  - Miscellaneous "B" - letters and receipts; almost all personal, with bits of Stone Printing, 1904 -1908, 1911 -1914; (3 folders) (Box Box 399)
  - Letters and invoices "C" - letters about personal matters - change of address to magazine companies, etc., 1912 -1916; (2 folders) (Box Box 399)
  - National Exchange Bank - bank notes and canceled checks, plus some correspondence, 1897 -1908 (Box Box 400)
  - Roanoke Knitting Mill - about a loan request and a deed, 1903 -1907 (Box Box 400)
  - Roanoke Railway & Electric Co. - chiefly about power for the Stone Printing plant, 1907 -1908 (Box Box 400)
  - Southern Stamp & Stationary Co. - about printing methods, 1907 -1908 (Box Box 400)
  - Southwest Virginia Trust - information on meetings, stock assessments, etc. sent to Stone as a shareholder, 1902 -1908 (Box Box 400)
  - Miscellaneous "S" - single and a few personal letters to and from: R. H. Solde, Southern Exploration Co., Somerville & Co. (real estate) speeches, Spencers Seedless Apples, Frank A. Stallman, Jordan Stabler Co. (fruit), A. C. Stansill, A. P. Staples, C. H. Stanley, Standorette, 1900 -1907 (Box Box 400)
  - Relief Fund - letters from virtually everyone seeking financial aid or community support for wartime projects, 1917 -1920 (Box Box 401)
  - Rotary Club of Roanoke - announcements of meetings and information to members of upcoming events, 1920 -1921 (Box Box 401)
  - Railway Business Assoc. - repeated (3) attempts to persuade Stone to join this group appeared to have failed, 1920 (Box Box 401)
  - Edward Regele (Salem) - Stone responds to a letter meant for Comas Cigarette Co. shareholders but sent to Stone by mistake; criticizes machinists unions; includes several copies of his reply, 1920 (Box Box 401)
  - A. Stone - a collection of personal letters (about insurance, household purchases, etc.), belonging to Stone's brother Al, 1904 -1916; (2 folders) (Box Box 401)
  - Miscellaneous "K" - private correspondence, especially with: A. J. Kennard, Henry P. Kendall, Kinetic Electric Co., Capt. William H. Kahle, 1912 -1913 (Box Box 402)
  - Liberty loans - clippings, speeches, circular letters and a poster they says: "Lend the way they fight.", 1917 -1919 (Box Box 402)
  - Miscellaneous "L" - personal correspondence, incl League for Industrial Rights, Harry Lowe, F. H. La Baume, League to Enforce Peace, John S. Lewis, Louis Lang, Dr. J. Thomas Lippincott, Llewellyns, W. P. Lipscomb, Levitt & Pierce, W. H. Lewis, 1912 -1919 (Box Box 402)
  - Magazines - subscription offers, 1917 -1918 (Box Box 402)
  - Menu cards - souvenirs from trains and restaurants, 1919 (Box Box 402)
  - Monthly letters to "Our Boys" - Stone joined a program to send a letter each month to men in the A.E.F.; including are his responses, censored and sent by "soldier's mail" from France and elsewhere, 1918 (Box Box 402)
  - Miscellaneous "E" - personal letters to/from: Ebert & Gary, William J. Eynon, 1915 -1920 (Box Box 403)
  - Miscellaneous "F" - personal correspondence, especially with: T. T. Fishburn, W. M. Fellers, Edgar Fergusson, U. M. Fowler, 1918 -1921 (Box Box 403)
  - Federal Trade Commission - a copy of the UTA's reply to charges of illegal activities made by the FTC, 1919 (Box Box 403)
  - Miscellaneous "G" - contains: Mr. Gooch's letter (expressing sympathy on his passing), Walter B. Guy (attorney), golf (with a rule book), 1916 -1921 (Box Box 403)
  - Motor cars - brochures and advertisement along with some correspondence about purchases and delivery, 1904 -1909 (Box Box 403)
  - French orphans - letters to and from Stone's otherwise fatherless foster children in France, 1919 -1920 (Box Box 403)
  - Miscellaneous "M" - personal correspondence with H. G. Mundy, J. Kyle Montague, William N. Moreau, Claude Moore, T. C. Morton, etc., 1901 -1907 (Box Box 403)
  - National Association of Manufacturers - circular letters and news of organizations and current issues, 1902 -1908 (Box Box 403)
  - Roanoke Industrial and Agricultural Assoc., 1902 -1907 (Box Box 404)
  - Miscellaneous "S", 1908 -1916; (5 folders) (Box Box 404)
  - Miscellaneous "S-T", 1907 -1908 (Box Box 404)
  - Miscellaneous "E", 1911 -1914 (Box Box 405)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "E" and Stone, 1918 -1920 (Box Box 405)
  - Davis & Stephenson, 1919 -1920 (Box Box 405)
  - Charles Diesinger - diamonds, 1914 (Box Box 405)
  - Miscellaneous "C" and investment companies, 1913 -1920 (Box Box 405)
  - Commerce and finance newspaper, 1920 (Box Box 405)
  - Miscellaneous "D-E", 1917 -1920 (Box Box 405)
  - Miscellaneous "C" and country clubs, 1920 (Box Box 405)
  - Motor cars, 1909 -1911 (Box Box 406)
  - Magazine ads, 1910 (Box Box 406)
  - Miscellaneous "M", 1910 -1911; (2 folders) (Box Box 406)
  - The Merchants Journal, 1909 (Box Box 406)
  - Merchant Marine Committee, 1911 (Box Box 406)
  - Miller, 1910 -1911 (Box Box 406)
  - Joseph Murray, 1909 -1910 (Box Box 406)
  - Miscellaneous "K-L", 1906 -1916 (Box Box 407)
  - Miscellaneous "L-M", 1904 -1912 (Box Box 407)
  - Edward L. Stone - plans for personal identification tag for books, 1913 (Box Box 408)
  - Edward L. Stone - telegrams, certificates, and lists of all the magazines he subscribed to, of all the clubs he belonged to, and of all the companies he owned, 1920 (Box Box 408)
  - Samples of printing jobs - mostly accounting sheets, no date (Box Box 408)
  - A. Stone: invoices and correspondence - personal business, 1918 -1919 (Box Box 408)
  - A. Stone: letters and invoices "M-Z" - personal business, 1918 -1923 (Box Box 408)
  - Miscellaneous "H" - personal correspondence with: Halsey & Co., J. G. Holland, R. A. Hughes, Frank A. Hill, John C. Cahill, John. M. Hart, Henry Street Property, 1911 -1919; (2 folders) (Box Box 409)
  - Food Administration, 1917 (Box Box 409)
  - Roanoke Country Club: Miscellaneous "A", 1912 (Box Box 410)
  - Roanoke Country Club: Miscellaneous "B", 1916 (Box Box 410)
  - Roanoke Country Club: Miscellaneous "C", 1915 -1917 (Box Box 410)
  - Roanoke Country Club: Miscellaneous "D-F", 1912 -1914 (Box Box 410)
  - The Director magazine, 1919 -1920 (Box Box 411)
  - WSS Honor Roll, 1918 (Box Box 411)
  - Thrift Newsletter, 1919 (Box Box 411)
  - Wartime Savings Stamps (WSS) - literature from Treasury Dept., correspondence and expenses, 1919; (2 folders) (Box Box 411)
  - Correspondence with Treasury Dept. concerning the WSS campaign; Ed Stone - regional director, 1913 -1919; (2 folders) (Box Box 411)
  - Miscellaneous letters - all to, by, or about the Johnson Coal Mining Co., an outfit which Stone owned for some time, 1912 -1913; (2 folders) (Box Box 412)
  - Miscellaneous "S", 1913 -1919 (Box Box 413)
  - Miscellaneous "C", 1916-1919; (2 folders) (Box Box 413)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1914 (Box Box 413)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia, 1919 (Box Box 413)
  - H. A. Miller, 1918 (Box Box 414)
  - Miscellaneous "A", 1918 (Box Box 414)
  - Miscellaneous "F" - including a newspaper on oil investment, the Oil Investor, 1918 -1919 (Box Box 414)
  - Miscellaneous "D", 1918 (Box Box 414)
  - Mercersburg Academy, Pennsylvania, 1918 (Box Box 414)
  - Miscellaneous "B", 1919 (Box Box 414)
  - Hub Wyoming Oil Co., including newspaper clippings on oil investment, the Oil Investor, 1919 (Box Box 414)
  - Miscellaneous "E", 1919 (Box Box 414)
  - Miscellaneous "G", 1918 -1919 (Box Box 414)
  - Miscellaneous "C", 1905 -1909, 1918 -1919 (Box Box 414)
  - Miscellaneous "K", 1918 -1919 (Box Box 414)
  - Miscellaneous "P", 1919 -1920 (Box Box 414)
  - Miscellaneous "J", 1918 (Box Box 414)
  - C. W. Schultz, 1906 (Box Box 414)
  - Small Grain Distilling Co., 1909 -1910 (Box Box 414)
  - Saturday Evening Post, 1910 (Box Box 414)
  - Scholl Lithographing Co., Williamsport, Penn., 1909; (2 folders) (Box Box 414)
  - Rev. Lunch, 1910 (Box Box 415)
  - Miscellaneous "L", 1910 -1913 (Box Box 415)
  - Seo Baune, 1907 -1910 (Box Box 415)
  - Miscellaneous "M", 1911 -1913; (3 folders) (Box Box 415)
  - Miscellaneous "G", 1903 -1912; (4 folders) (Box Box 416)
  - Florida land companies - interesting material on land investment in Florida, 1910 (Box Box 416)
  - Miscellaneous "F", 1909 -1910 (Box Box 416)
  - Miscellaneous "F, G, T-V, X-Z", 1915 -1920 (Box Box 416)
  - Miscellaneous "A", 1918 -1919 (Box Box 416)
  - Miscellaneous "A-C", 1918 -1920 (Box Box 416)
  - Miscellaneous "K-N, P, R", 1917 -1920 (Box Box 416)
  - Text of William Stone's trip to England, ca. 1910 (Box Box 417)
  - Miscellaneous publishing companies, 1930 (Box Box 417)
  - Booklists and assorted correspondence from printers, also a list of books in the library of E. Stone, 1931 (Box Box 417)
  - Miscellaneous "S", including photos, 1934 -1936; (3 folders) (Box Box 420)
  - Joseph Richardson, 1911 (Box Box 420)
  - National Exchange Bank - about management matters, 1919 -1920 (Box Box 421)
  - Roanoke Hospital - about donations, 1910 -1915 (Box Box 422)
  - Roanoke Railway & Electric Co. - about demonstrations and employee benefits, 1909 -1913 (Box Box 422)
  - Miscellaneous "R" - personal and private business correspondence with: Roanoke Overalls Co., Roanoke Light Infantry Co., Philip Ruxton Inc. (Inkers), Roycroft Shop (printing club), Roanoke County Telephone Co., Roanoke Gas & Water Co., Clarence G. Rose, J. W. Roberts, Roanoke Gun Club, 1908 -1915; (2 folders) (Box Box 422)
  - Correspondence "J" - private, personal correspondence between Stone and: Mr. and Mrs. L. D. James, Harlean James, Japan Paper Co., William J. Jencks, Mr. and Mrs. Clem D. Johnston, Mr. E. R. Johnson and family, 1932 -1935 (Box Box 423)
  - L. R. Johnston - private correspondence with this photographer-artist in White Sulphur Springs, 1932 -1935 (Box Box 423)
  - Correspondence "M" - personal correspondence, mostly about books, with: Mrs. Blanche Melland, Metropolitan Life Insurance Co., memorandums, W. E. Mingea, 1930 -1935 (Box Box 423)
  - Receipts, foreign and other matter, 1914 (Box Box 424)
  - Roanoke Country Club, 1913 -1914; (2 folders) (Box Box 424)
  - City of Roanoke, 1914 (Box Box 424)
  - Rotary Club, 1914 -1915 (Box Box 424)
  - Railroad companies with regard to tariffs, 1913 -1914 (Box Box 424)
  - Roanoke Automobile Co. - Stone purchases 2 Cadillacs, 1914 (Box Box 424)
  - Roanoke Automobile Assoc., 1910 -1914 (Box Box 424)
  - Rev. Arthur Rowbotham, 1914 -1915 (Box Box 424)
  - Miscellaneous "C'', 1913 -1915 (Box Box 425)
  - Thomas Clemmitt, printer, 1909 -1916 (Box Box 425)
  - J. E. Catlin, 1913 -1915 (Box Box 425)
  - Rev. W. Campbell, 1912 -1915 (Box Box 425)
  - Crystal Spring Land Co., 1914 -1915 (Box Box 425)
  - Caldwell Sites Co., 1912 -1915 (Box Box 425)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia, B. A. James, 1910 -1913 (Box Box 425)
  - James Cassell, 1903 -1915 (Box Box 425)
  - City of Roanoke, 1912 (Box Box 425)
  - Savings Societies, 1918 (Box Box 426)
  - Clubs and organizations, 1917 -1918 (Box Box 426)
  - Edward Stone, 1918 (Box Box 426)
  - Sales of war bonds, 1917 -1918 (Box Box 426)
  - Wartime saving stamps correspondence, 1918 -1919; (2 folders) (Box Box 426)
  - Wartime saving stamps sales, 1913 (Box Box 426)
  - Receipts, 1918 (Box Box 426)
  - Insurance companies, 1913 (Box Box 426)
  - Osceola Lodge - club news, 1915 (Box Box 427)
  - Navy League of the U.S. - membership information on this national defense organization, 1915 -1916 (Box Box 427)
  - Miscellaneous "T-Z" - letters about typewriters, the Times, etc., 1915 -1917 (Box Box 427)
  - Miscellaneous "N-S" - railway meetings, and other business, 1915 -1918 (Box Box 427)
  - Miscellaneous "L-M" - including the Municipal League, 1916 (Box Box 427)
  - Miscellaneous "F-G" - letters, magazine offers, club news, 1915 -1916 (Box Box 427)
  - Miscellaneous "C" - loan application, bond offers and tailor samples, 1915 -1917 (Box Box 427)
  - National Industrial Conference - letters and speeches, 1917 (Box Box 427)
  - Roanoke Times - financial records, 1910 -1915 (Box Box 428)
  - Miscellaneous - about personal business, like house painting and magazine subscriptions, 1914 -1915 (Box Box 428)
  - Stocks and bonds - investment information, 1915, 1917; (2 folders) (Box Box 428)
  - Stone's Impressions - letters about this little publication, 1912 -1914 (Box Box 428)
  - Streets and roads - about campaign by Roanoke's auto owners to improve roads; photographs, 1915 -1916 (Box Box 428)
  - Stage - programs and playbills, 1917 (Box Box 429)
  - Miscellaneous "B" - personal files of letters, including "Bureau of Municipal Research", Mrs. Anna P. Bell, Baltic and other miscellaneous European data, 1911 -1914 (Box Box 430)
  - Clippings and comments - humorous and inspirational quotes as well as practical advice (how to judge value of pearl necklaces), 1912 -1914 (Box Box 430)
  - Confederate Reunion - letters, and souvenirs from the groups functions, 1913 (Box Box 430)
  - Subjects "C" - personal miscellaneous; contains a "style book" - fashion magazine - for 1914, 1913 -1914 (Box Box 430)
  - Stone: letters and miscellaneous - personal nature, 1913; (3 folders) (Box Box 431)
  - W. B. Bevill - personal correspondence, 1912 -1915 (Box Box 432)
  - Miscellaneous - especially on water power, 1914 -1915 (Box Box 433)
  - Southwest Virginia Booklet - about the publication of a booklet called "The Beckoning Land", 1914 -1915 (Box Box 433)
  - Manufacturers Club - about membership and upcoming events, 1915 -1916 (Box Box 433)
  - League to Enforce Peace - promotional letters, 1914 -1916 (Box Box 433)
  - Letters "B" - personal correspondence, especially with: W. G. Baldwin, W. S. Battle, Bartlett Tours Co., W. W. Boxley, Samuel Budd, Thomas Branch & Co., Belleview-Stratford, Ogden Brower, 1917 -1920 (Box Box 434)
  - Clippings and comments - some about Stone's contributions to Roanoke, etc., 1919 -1921 (Box Box 434)